# **Fariz Afif**

## **Back End Developer**

▼ Tangerang Selatan, 15225
Image: Farizalis@hotmail.com
Image: O85719492262
Image: Farizalis@hotmail.com
I

🗘 farizaiis 🥆 Simple Contact

#### **Education**

08/2021 – 12/2021	<b>Back End Developer,</b> Glints Academy
06/2013 - 06/2014	Social Science, PKBM Alifyah Jakarta

### **Summary**

I am a person who likes logic and technology. As a Back End Developer, I've made Rest API for Movie App and DietOn App when I study at Glints Academy. Before joining Bootcamp, I had experience in the entertainment field as a Project Officer and Account Executive in Event Organizer Company for 6 years to maintain a Project or Program.

## Languages

• Indonesian (Native)

• English (Profesional Working Proficiency)

## **Professional Experience**

06/2021	- 08/2021
Jakarta.	Indonesia

### **Account Executive,** Vision Organizer

Part of Vision Organizer as Account Executive

My list client: KT&G, OLX, Mizone

- Maintain program as Client Request
- Maintain exciting Client to increase get more Company Revenue
- Find new Client to expand through Company Relation

## 11/2014 – 05/2021 Jakarta, Indonesia

#### **Project Officer,** Redwhite Indonesia

As a Freelance Project Officer for 6 years at *Redwhite Indonesia* that control Project like Brand Activation, Press Conference for Disney, Gala Premiere Disney, Music Event, and anything that client Request for their Event My list client: Disney, Indosat, Telkomsel, Axis, BRI, Mandiri

- Manage program to running as Client Request
- Manage team member like Crew, Vendor, and Production Team to complete their job
- Solve any problem that relate with our Event

## 03/2020 – 07/2020 Jakarta, Indonesia

#### Account Executive, TemuRasa

Part of Temurasa as Account Executive

My list client: Meikarta, Sawit, Sayurbox

- Maintain program as Client Request
- Maintain exciting Client to increase get more Company Revenue
- Find new Client to expand through Company Relation

## **Develops Project**

10/2021 – 11/2021 **DietOn** 

An App that controls users Diet Progress. Users can check their Weight and Measurement progress, set how many Calorie can consume, set Meal Plan for check how many Calorie has consumed, set Exercise Plan so they can set Alert

when they need to do Exercise

Documentation Link: https://bit.ly/DocumentationDietOn

10/2021 – 10/2021 **Movie App** 

Build a Movie App like IMDB, where users can leave a review like comment and rate the movie in this App. Users can check movies they have already

reviewed and they can check another users too

Documentation Link: https://bit.ly/DocumentationMovieApp

## Other Project and Experience

2019 – 2020	Telkomsel ByU Activation Ground, ByUx Superfox
2017 - 2018	<b>Jenius Activation Ground,</b> <i>Double Tape x Jenius</i>
2018	Mudik Bareng Pertamina, LARISA
2016	<b>Oppo Selfie Fest with NetTV,</b> NetTV x Oppo
2016	Indonesia Motor Show, Seven Api
2016	Gaikindo Indonesia International Auto Show, Seven Api
2015	Gaikindo Indonesia International Auto Show, Seven API
2015	Indonesia International Moto Show, Diandra

## Skills

ExpressJs	NodeJs
Object Oriented	Sequelize
Mongoose	MySQL
SQL	PostgreSQL
File Upload	Socket.io
CI/CD	Heroku
Git	Postman
Swagger	Adobe PS
Javascript	Redis
Supertest	Jest
Cloudinary	